David Fuentez

Computer Engineer

LinkedIn Profile: <u>linkedin.com/in/name</u>

daniel367daniel367@gmail.com +504-9825-2225

⊕

Click here for my portfolio

PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a Software Developer, ERP Systems, mobile applications and Web Applications. Skilled in data analysis, software engineering. Solid education professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from the Technological University of Honduras. English teacher with demonstrable experience in the non-profit management sector.

Academic Education



Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science | Universidad Tecnológica de Honduras

Completion date May 2024

Work Experience



Software Developer: DaHu Company Services

January 2022 to January 2024 (2 years)

- Mobile and Web Application Developer:
 - Mobile application development to share information about projects in the NGO.
 - Web application development for the management of projects in the organization.
 - Web application development for the administrative and information management of a school.
 - o Construction of user interface, database development, implementation of API's.
 - Technologies used: NextJS, Vercel, JavaScript, Dart, Flutter, Firebase, JSON, GIT, GitHub.
- Management Software Developer for a company that buys and sells coffee.
 - Development of a management system for the control of sales, inventories, suppliers, reports and invoicing of a coffee company.
 - User interface construction, database development, API's implementation.
 - Environments: Java, C#, C++, JavaScript, Next.js, CSS, HTML, Firebase, GIT, GitHub, node.js.

Accounting Assistant - Blessing to the Nations Ministry

January 2022 to January 2024 (2 years)

- Financial reporting and organization of financial backups.
- Project statistics to generate new ideas and new projects.

Teacher/Tutor | Proyecto Nueva Vida

From January 2020 to December 2023 (3 years and 10 months).

- Computer Science and Mathematics classes from 2nd to 9th grade.
- Achievements: Increased individual student performance.
- Planning of the class schedule.

Certifications

Certification in NDG Linux Essentials y NDG Linux Unhatched | Cisco Networking Academy

• 2023

Certification in 5G tecnologies, AI, Cloud Computing y HMS | Huawei, Seeds for The Future Class octubre 2022

Program Seeds for the Future from Huawei.

Certification in Master en JavaScript: Aprender JS, jQuery, Angular, NodeJS

UDEMY Junio 2023

Certification in Typescript: The Complete developers Guide

• UDEMY Junio 2023

Skills

- Developer in Flutter, Net Maui, LAMP, HTML, CSS JavaScript, Java, C# environments.
- Java, HTML, CSS, Python, Excel, Firebase, MySQL, Oracle Database, NextJs, Microsoft Word.
- Experience in Adobe Photoshop and video editing.

Languages

English Language

- Intermediate oral level (conversational).
- Intermediate written level (conversational).

Spanish Language

Native

Volunteers

- Volunteer at Samaritans Purse, Operation Christmas Child children's charity program.
- Project leader at Ministry Blessing to the Nations, in the Agua Pura project, to provide 500 families living in remote communities with access to clean water in Honduras.
- I have participated as an English to Spanish interpreter in medical and social brigades in remote communities in Honduras.